(Sheldon:)...that spot at the moment I first sat on it
would be zero, zero, zero, zero.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)Don't sit in his spot.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Fine. Happy?
(Sheldon:)I'm not unhappy.
(Penny:)Boy, I love him,
but he is one serious whackadoodle.
(Leonard:)Okay, that should do it.
(Penny:)Oh, thank you. You are a lifesaver.
(Leonard:)That's a lot of shoes you ordered.
(Penny:)Yeah, you know the sad thing is,
it's really not.
(Penny:)Ooh, is this one of those paintball guns?
You ought to come with us sometime.
(Penny:)Oh, no, thanks. I'm from Nebraska.
(Penny:)When we shoot things,
we wanna eat them...
(Penny:)...or make them leave
our boyfriends alone. Ha, ha.
[PAINTBALLS FIRE]
PENNY:
Oh.